Indiana University Graduate Library School Dean's records, 1961-1992 C167
Indiana University Archives
- Research and Study Proposals, 1966-1982; undated (Box 5)
  - ERIC [Education Resources Information Center] Research, 1969-1977 (Box 6)
    - Evaluation Study Products and Services - First Quarterly Report, May-July 1970; September-October 1970 (Box 6)
    - Investigation, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Proposals, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Research, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Study, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Study - Plot, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Study Clearinghouses, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Study Foreign Journals Programs and Printouts, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Study Input, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Study Printouts for Preliminary Sample from Ulrich's (N=594), 1977 (Box 6)
    - Study - Reading Resource Network Centers, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Study, Standing Orders, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Study USOE Supported Collections, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Study, State Departments of Education, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Proposals - Research Center for Library and Information Science (RCLIS) ERIC Evaluation Study, 1970-1972 (Box 6)
  - National Science Foundation, 1972-1978 (Box 7)
    - Colloquia, June 12, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 7)
    - New York Meeting, May 1, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Project Background, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
    - Journal Study Background, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Journal Study, Corresp. Re: Publication of Final Report, 1974-1976 (Box 7)
    - Journal Study (Box 7)
      - Notes, 1974 (Box 7)
      - Questionnaires, 1974; (1) (Box 7)
      - Questionnaire, 1974; (2 - backup) (Box 7)
      - Questionnaire, 1974; (3 - Instruments, etc.) (Box 7)
      - Questionnaire (Foreign), 1974-1975 (Box 7)
    - Research Proposal A Proposal to Study the Economics and Interaction of the Publisher-Library Relationship in the Production and Use of Scholarly & Research Journals, September 1973 (Box 7)
    - Research Proposal, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Research Proposals...Journal Acquisition and Retention, 1976-1977 (Box 7)
    - Report, ALA Midwinter, RTSD, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Study (Box 7)
      - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 7)
      - Interview Guide, 1974 (Box 7)
      - Study and Correspondence with Lee Burchinal, 1974-1976 (Box 7)
      - Correspondence re: Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 7)
    - Preliminary Drafts/Proposals/Research Center for Library and Information Science (RCLIS) (Box 7)
      - Publisher Library Relationship (National Science Foundation), 1972-1974 (Box 7)
    - Proposals - Research Center for Library and Information Science (RCLIS) (Box 7)
      - Boyer Dissertation (National Science Foundation), 1972-1974 (Box 7)
      - Policy Anal. Bibliography. (NSF), 1973 (Box 7)
  - Student Dissertation and Research Proposals, 1972-1978 (Box 7)
    - Boyer, Calvin J., Dissertation Proposal, 1974-1976 (Box 7)
    - Doctoral Dissertations Proposals, 1972-1974 (Box 7)
    - Libbey, Miles, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Mowery, Judith, Dissertation Proposal, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Restricted Materials (Box 8)
    - Restricted Materials (Box 9)